<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<group
		xmlns="tag:rayrobdod.name,2014-10-04:Script"
		xmlns:ext="tag:rayrobdod.name,2014-10-04:ScriptSample"
>
	<!-- assuming location/forest is set -->
	<group id="intro" >
		<speak speaker="Voice in Your Head" >
			Sunlight filters down through the canopy. There is a
			young girl in the center of the clearing. The turns an
			object in her hands, and light dances off of both it and
			her face.
		</speak>
	</group>
	
	<group id="talk" >
		<speak if-not-flag="female" speaker="Ellie" >
			Do ya see this mister? It's so pretty and reflective.
			Why, I'd bet it's the shiniest shiny that ever did shine.
		</speak>
		<speak if-flag="female" speaker="Ellie" >
			Do ya see this ma'am? It's so pretty and reflective.
			Why, I'd bet it's the shiniest shiny that ever did shine.
		</speak>
		
		<speak if-flag="clearing/gaveAluminum" speaker="Voice in Your Head" >
			The girl shows you a piece of Aluminum Foil.
		</speak>
		<group if-not-flag="clearing/gaveAluminum">
			<speak if-not-flag="inventory/aluminum" speaker="Voice in Your Head" >
				The girl shows you a fishing lure.
			</speak>
			<group if-flag="inventory/aluminum" >
				<speak speaker="Voice in Your Head" >
					The girl shows you a fishing lure. In response, you
					show her the piece of Aluminum Foil. She drops the
					fishing lure.
				</speak>
				<speak speaker="Ellie" >
					Wow. That's even shinier! Can I have it? Pwease? 
				</speak>
				<speak speaker="Voice in Your Head" >
					You give her the aluminum foil. You then go to pick
					up the fishing lure. 
				</speak>
				<setFlag flag="clearing/gaveAluminum" />
				<setFlag flag="inventory/aluminum" value="0" />
				<speak speaker="Ellie" >
					Oh, yeah. I have this shiny now so I don't need that
					one. Go ahead. 
				</speak>
				<setFlag flag="inventory/lure" />
			</group>
		</group>
	</group>
	
	<group id="contemplate" >
		<speak speaker="Voice in Your Head" >
			It is rather relaxing here. You lie down.
		</speak>
		<speak speaker="Voice in Your Head" >
			You begin to contemplate the universe and
			its infinite mysteries.
		</speak>
		<speak speaker="Voice in Your Head" >
			You haven't been here that long, but you still 
			think the Sun should have noticably moved in the
			time you've been here.
		</speak>
		<speak speaker="Voice in Your Head" >
			In fact, you've never looked at whether you produce
			a shadow. It would probably be jaring if you didn't,
			and even the most primitive 3D games draw shadows.
		</speak>
		<speak speaker="Voice in Your Head" >
			You actually look, and realize you're not producing
			a shadow.
		</speak>
		<speak speaker="Voice in Your Head" >
			In fact, you're not actually looking at where your
			shadow should be. You're looking at a console terminal
			that is telling you that you're looking at your shadow.
		</speak>
		<speak speaker="Voice in Your Head" >
			You check really carefully at the previous string
			of characters in hopes of finding an incorrect usage
			of "you're" or "your" so that you may yell at whoever
			wrote it about correct "your/you're" usage.
		</speak>
		<speak speaker="Voic            ad" >
			"String". That word sounded important.
			Or looked important. Whichever. You grab a few
			characters off the console terminal just in case. 
		</speak>
		<setFlag flag="inventory/string" />
		<speak speaker="Voice in Your Head" >
			One of the girl's shouts brings you out of
			your contemplative daze.
		</speak>
	</group>
</group>

