<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<group
		xmlns="tag:rayrobdod.name,2014-10-04:Script"
		xmlns:ext="tag:rayrobdod.name,2014-10-04:ScriptSample"
>
	<speak speaker="Prof. Redwood">
		Ah, hello. Welcome to the world of bits. A land filled with
		ones and zeros. My name, incase the interface hasn't told
		you already, is Professor Redwood. I'm known around these
		parts as The Bit Professor. 
	</speak>
	<speak speaker="Prof. Redwood" emotion="Embarrased">
		Now, my interface isn't working correctly, so it's not
		telling me your name. So, what is your name? 
	</speak>
	<!-- ext:setName / -->
	<speak speaker="Prof. Redwood">
		So your name is <ext:printName />, then? I'll try to remember
		that. Now, it wouldn't be a proper introduction if I didn't
		ask "Are you a boy or a girl?", but I don't particularly care,
		so let's just pretend I asked that and move on.
	</speak>
	<speak speaker="Prof. Redwood">
		You're going on a Fetch Quest. We're just making sure a thing
		works, so don't expect a lot of story. Your goal is to get
		the Giant Ruby. You'll start with nothing but your wits.
		Good Luck.
	</speak>
	<setFlag flag="inventory/wits" value="1" />
	<setFlag flag="location/river" value="1" />
	<speak speaker="Voice in your head">
		You materialze inside a natural park. You hear the sounds of
		a rushing river. You look around, and immediately catch the
		eye of another person.
	</speak>
	<speak speaker="George">
		Yeah, I see you eyeing my ruby. I found it, and it's going to
		feed me today. There aren't many days where I find somehting
		I can sell for food you know.
	</speak>
	<speak speaker="You">
		Have you heard of the saying "If you give a man a fish, you'll
		feed him for a day. If you teach a man -
	</speak>
	<speak speaker="George">
		yeahyeahyeah. I know how to fish, I don't have a fishing rod.
		I even know how to make one on the cheap - a lure, a rod, and
		some string. I don't know where to find those either.
	</speak>
	<speak speaker="You">
		If I find those three things for you, will you trade it for the ruby?
	</speak>
	<speak speaker="George">
		You know what? Sure. Find a lure, a rod, and some string and you
		can have the ruby.
	</speak>
	<speak speaker="Voice in Your Head" > What do? </speak>
	<goto href="mainMenu.xml" />
</group>
